[{"answer": " So, are you all ready for your visa interview", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I think so.  I have my appointment all set up and all the documents I need", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": " So, are you all ready for your visa interview", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Same here.  I hope it goes well, though.  Im worried I might be denied", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " I think so.  I have my appointment all set up and all the documents I need", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yeah, its hard not to worry about it.  I read an interesting article today abou", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Same here.  I hope it goes well, though.  Im worried I might be denied", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Oh yeah?  What did it say", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Yeah, its hard not to worry about it.  I read an interesting article today abou", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": "It was about ten things to remember when applying for a non-immigrant visa", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Oh yeah?  What did it say", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Do you remember what they were", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 27, "question": "It was about ten things to remember when applying for a non-immigrant visa", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " I think so.  The first was ties to your home country.  It said that well have t", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Do you remember what they were", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " How do we do that", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 36, "question": " I think so.  The first was ties to your home country.  It said that well have t", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Well, wed want to talk about anything that binds us to our home country", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 37, "question": " How do we do that", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I plan to work with my familys business back home after I graduate.  Do yo", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Well, wed want to talk about anything that binds us to our home country", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Yes, I think things like that are what theyre looking for.  Another point wa", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I plan to work with my familys business back home after I graduate.  Do yo", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Yes, I think things like that are what theyre looking for.  Another point wa", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " It said that we should be prepared to answer all questions in English and no", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What do you mean", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK.  I wasnt planning on doing that anyways", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 54, "question": " It said that we should be prepared to answer all questions in English and no", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Me neither.  Another point was know your program and how it fits into you", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 55, "question": " OK.  I wasnt planning on doing that anyways", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I guess Ill have to plan for that question.  I hadnt really thought about it", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Me neither.  Another point was know your program and how it fits into you", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yeah, it sounds like we really have to know our stuff.  That reminds me o", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " I guess Ill have to plan for that question.  I hadnt really thought about it", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I heard the visa interview only lasts five minutes of less, so I guess thats why", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yeah, it sounds like we really have to know our stuff.  That reminds me o", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Thats right.  Another thing I remember is about employment.  The articl", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 66, "question": " I heard the visa interview only lasts five minutes of less, so I guess thats why", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Even though were allowed to work on-campus and off-campus wit", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Thats right.  Another thing I remember is about employment.  The articl", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " I guess we just need to keep in mind that studying is our purpose and mai", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Even though were allowed to work on-campus and off-campus wit", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " OK.  Ill keep that in mind then", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 79, "question": " I guess we just need to keep in mind that studying is our purpose and mai", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " The last thing I remember was about a visa denial", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 83, "question": " OK.  Ill keep that in mind then", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Oh, no.  What did it say", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 84, "question": " The last thing I remember was about a visa denial", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " It said that no matter what the outcome, dont argue with the visa officer", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Oh, no.  What did it say", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " I really hope I dont have to deal with a denial", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 91, "question": " It said that no matter what the outcome, dont argue with the visa officer", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I know.  Me too.  Hopefully, we wont have to.  Anyways, thats all I remembe", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 92, "question": " I really hope I dont have to deal with a denial", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " It was pretty helpful.  Those are all good points to keep in mind during our vis", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 94, "question": " I know.  Me too.  Hopefully, we wont have to.  Anyways, thats all I remembe", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " I thought so too", "docId": "04-10", "aSentId": 100, "question": " It was pretty helpful.  Those are all good points to keep in mind during our vis", "qSentId": 99}]
